Guide to the Records of The New York Institute for the Humanities RG.37.4
New York University Archives
Records of the New York Institute for the Humanities
1971-2021
1980-1984
New York University Archives
New York Institute for the Humanities
RG.37.4
40.5 Linear Feet in 117 containers
932.81 Megabytes in 394 computer files
The New York Institute for the Humanities (NYIH) was founded at NYU in 1977. During its early years, the organization established weekly forums for fellows and guests, and public events. The core of the New York Institute for the Humanities (NYIH) program remains its weekly invitational Fellows Forums. The NYIH also sponsors public conferences, discussions, readings, lectures, and podcasts. The Records of the New York Institute for the Humanities document the formation and early years of the Institute, the activities of Institute Fellows, and the seminars, lectures, and other events sponsored by the Institute.
Conditions Governing Access
Administrative records and unpublished reports of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation (boxes 92-93). Access to files spanning multiple years will be opened to researchers based on the date of the most recent materials. Board of Trustees records are closed for 35 years from the date of creation. Materials related to personnel, grievances, job and fellowship searches and applications, and all files that fall under the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) are permanently restricted. Additional restrictions may apply to other materials in this collection. For questions regarding specific restrictions, please contact the University Archives.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The bulk of the materials were transferred from the New York Institute for the Humanities to the University Archives in 2002; the accession number related to this transfer is 02.010. Additional transfers of audio and video recordings were made in 2007 and 2018; the accession numbers related to these accretions are 07.013, 08.001, and 2019.008. Additional accretions were transferred in 2021 and 2022; the accession numbers associated with these accretions are 2021.022 and 2022.054. Some materials from RG 9.5.1, including event posters, correspondence, reports, and a grant application, were transferred in September 2024.
Arrangement
Folders are generally arranged alphabetically by folder title.
The records are grouped into three series, two of which have been further arranged into subseries. The series and subseries arrangement of the records is as follows:
Series I. Director's Files
Subseries IA. Administrative
Subseries IB. Individuals
Subseries IC. Institutions
Subseries ID. Subject Files
Series II. Seminars, Lectures, and Events
Series III. Audio and Video Recordings
Subseries IIIA. Cassette Tapes
Subseries IIIB. 1/4 Inch Reels
Subseries IIIC. Mini Disks
Subseries IIID. VHS Tapes
Historical Note
In the summer of 1976, New York University Professor of Sociology Richard Sennett chaired a conference on the Humanities and Social Thought in Bellagio, Italy. Sennett and other participants developed the idea for a New York-based institute to foster intellectual discourse and cross-disciplinary communication while at the conference. In December 1976 New York University and Richard Sennett's Center for Humanistic Studies co-sponsored the conference "The Future of the Intellectual Community in New York", which was co-organized by Sennett, New York University President John Sawhill, and New York University Professor Ronald Florence (then Director of the New York Council for the Humanities). Based on the success of the conference, Sennett and President Sawhill co-hosted a series of informal dinners for writers, artists, and leaders in various fields. Participants discussed how to continue to redefine and strengthen intellectual life in New York City. The ideas that arose from the dinners provided the structure for the New York Institute for the Humanities (NYIH). Correspondence about these dinners, and the first proposals for a New York Institute for the Humanities, can be found in the Administrative Papers of President John Crittenden Sawhill (RG 3.0.8), Box 44.
In 1977 the New York Institute for the Humanities was established as a permanent activity of New York University by an act of the University's Board of Trustees. An advisory board was formed to help with the Institute's early development, while Sennett, The New York Times editor Caroline Rand Herron, and New York University Humanities Professor Thomas Bender worked with administrative assistant Toni Greenberg on the Institute's day-to-day operations. Herron acted as a publications and communications consultant, creating a series of Institute lunches and public forums. Bender also contributed considerable time and organized the Institute's first Gallatin Lectures. In 1978, the Institute received significant funding from the Exxon Education Foundation and the National Endowment for the Humanities, enabling expansion of its Fellowship and Lecture activities. In 1980 the Institute was independently incorporated and formed its own Board of Trustees; however, all daily administrative activities were handled by New York University, with the Institute's Board serving primarily in an advisory role.
From the time of the Institute's inception, the Fellowship program was the core of the New York Institute for the Humanities, embodying its mission to support the work of individual scholars and intellectuals in an environment which encouraged interaction. About half of the early Fellows were academics from New York-area universities, while the rest were artists, writers, journalists, and public officials. In the early years, fellows generally met once or twice a month for informal seminars. As the Institute grew, Sennett worked with Aryeh Neier and Bender to create a more defined program in which Fellows--elected to either one-year or five-year fellowships--formed interdisciplinary seminars around topics of interest and participated in weekly Fellows Lunches. Most Fellows were unpaid, although some received office space or clerical support. Fellows were responsible for the Institute's internal operations, which were overseen by the Director and three committees: an Executive Committee, a Program Committee, and a Fellowship Selection Committee.
The Program Committee was particularly active during the Institute's first five years. The Institute hosted public lecture series and conferences, most notably the James Lecture Series and the Gallatin Lecture Series. In a concerted move to counter American isolationist tendencies at the time, the James Lectures brought primarily European intellectuals to the Institute. The Gallatin Lecture Series was created shortly thereafter to provide an audience for American humanists. The period of 1979-1983 was especially active, bringing such literary and intellectual figures as Michel Foucault, Italo Calvino, Czeslow Milosz, Jorge Luis Borges and Roland Barthes to speak publicly and to participate in seminars. In 1981 the Institute launched a Humanities Exchange Program for writers exiled from Latin American and Eastern European regimes. Many of the Institute's early lectures were published by Columbia University Press in Humanities in Review (1982), edited by David Rieff.
The core of the New York Institute for the Humanities program remains its weekly invitational Fellows Forums. The NYIH also sponsors public conferences, discussions, readings, lectures, and podcasts. In 2020, facing a financial crisis triggered by the pandemic, NYU ended its sponsorship of the NYIH. This decision went into effect in 2021. Under the guidance of a new board of directors, the NYIH has reorganized as a tax-exempt organization and formed a connection with the New York Public Library.
Sources:
Administrative Papers of President John Crittenden Sawhill, 1974-1981, (RG 3.0.8) New York University Archives
Benn, Melissa "Inner City Scholar" The Guardian Saturday February 3, 2001
"History." New York Institute for the Humanities, accessed September 17, 2024, https://nyihumanities.org/history.
Rieff, David. Humanities in Review Cambridge: New York Institute for the Humanities, 1982
Biographical Note
As founder of the Institute, Richard Sennett's papers form a large part of this collection. Sennett, an interdisciplinary scholar, novelist, and social critic, is currently Professor of History and Sociology at New York University, and Professor of Sociology and Chair of the Cities Programme at the London School of Economics. Born in Chicago in 1943, Sennett studied sociology at Harvard University. After brief appointments at Yale and Brandeis Universities, he came to New York University in 1972, where he has spent the majority of his career. Sennett has written over a dozen books on subjects ranging from urbanism to modern capitalism, including The Hidden Injuries of Class (1972), The Fall of Public Man (1976), and Authority, as well as the novel The Frog Who Dared to Croak (1982).
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to some audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted. An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Scope and Contents
The Records of the New York Institute for the Humanities consists of materials created and collected by the organization from its inception, ca. 1976, through 2013. Materials related to the administration of the organization, sponsored events, and information on new fellows are included. These materials consist of event posters, press releases, budgets, grant proposals, and correspondence; fellows' directories and photographs; Executive Committee meeting minutes; and drafts of the protoype of the journal, Omnivore. In addition to materials relating to the operation and activities of the Institute, the collection contains a large number of documents generated by Professor Richard Sennett, founder and former Director of the Institute.
Arts and society; Humanities; Symposia; Lectures.; Conferences.; Humanism.; Sociology.; Orlov, Yuri, 1924-; Poirier, Richard; Reich, Steve, 1936-; Rieff, David; Rubert de Ventós, Xavier; Sacks, Oliver, 1933-2015; Safdie, Moshe, 1938-; Sass, Louis Arnorsson; Sassen, Saskia; Sawhill, John C., 1936-; Schorske, Carl E.; Sennett, Richard, 1943-; Sieburth, Richard; Snitow, Ann Barr, 1943-; Sontag, Susan, 1933-2004; Spender, Stephen, 1909-1995; Glass, Philip; Turkel, Gerald; Gitlin, Todd; Turner, A. Richard (Almon Richard), 1932-2011; Habermas, Jürgen; Varnedoe, Kirk, 1946-2003; Gordimer, Nadine; Voinovich, Vladimir, 1932-; Haskell, Francis, 1928-2000; Hampshire, Stuart, 1914-2004; Ward, Eileen; Huxtable, Ada Louise; White, Edmund, 1940-; Hobsbawm, E. J. (Eric J.), 1917-2012; Wittig, Monique; Kos, Danilo, 1935-1989; Kamm, F. M. (Frances Myrna); Milosz, Czesław; Menuhin, Yehudi, 1916-1999; Naipaul, V. S. (Vidiadhar Surajprasad), 1932-2018; Moravia, Alberto, 1907-1990; Nochlin, Linda; Neier, Aryeh, 1937-; Baritz, Loren, 1928-; Bender, Thomas, 1944-; Calvino, Italo; Derrida, Jacques; Borges, Jorge Luis, 1899-1986; Brodsky, Joseph, 1940-1996; Foucault, Michel, 1926-1984; Geertz, Clifford; Dorsen, Norman; FitzGerald, Frances, 1940-; Wahl, Nicholas; Rorty, Richard; Breytenbach, Breyten; Kapuściński, Ryszard
- Series I. Director's Files, 1971-2013
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of records generated by the director's office and its staff. These records are related to both the administration of the Institute as well as non-Institute matters associated with the professional career of the director. Richard Sennett generated the majority of the early documents in this series. Many of these files relate to his career as an academic and a writer outside of his capacity as director, such as correspondence with publishers and conference organizers. Most of the materials from accretions were created by subsequent directors. These files consist of Executive Committee meeting minutes and correspondence, by-laws and certificate of incorporation, budgets, annual reports, other committee meeting minutes and correspondence (including the Membership Committee, Program Committee, and the Fellowship Committee), and general correspondence.
  - Subseries IA. Administrative, 1971-2013
    - Accounting Problems, 1980-1982; cuid4371 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Accounting Problems, 1982-1983; cuid4372 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Action Memos, 1981-1982; cuid4373 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Administrative Handbook, circa 2001 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Advisory Board, 1977; cuid4374 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Advisory Board, 1978-1979; cuid4375 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports, 1978-1981 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1982-1985 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report, 1999 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Apartment Rental, 1980-1981; cuid4376 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors -- Bakstansky, Peter, undated; cuid4377 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors -- Golden, William T., undated; cuid4378 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors -- Rose, Daniel, undated; cuid4379 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Board of Directors -- Smith, Roger R., undated; cuid4380 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors -- Soros, George, undated; cuid4381 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Board of Trustees -- Bylaws, undated; cuid4382 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Board of Trustees -- Fundraising, 1979-1983; cuid4383 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Board of Trustees -- General, 1977-1980; cuid4384 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Board of Trustees -- General, 1981-1984; cuid4385 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Board of Trustees -- Meeting, December 5, 1979; cuid4386 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Board of Trustees -- Meeting, April 7, 1980; cuid4387 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Board of Trustees -- Meeting, July 28, 1980; cuid4388 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Board of Trustees -- Meeting, November 4, 1980; cuid4389 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Board of Trustees -- Meeting, January 15, 1981; cuid4390 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Board of Trustees -- Meeting, April 8, 1981; cuid4391 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Board of Trustees -- Meeting, September 28, 1981; cuid4392 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Board of Trustees -- Meeting, October 28, 1981; cuid4393 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Board of Trustees -- Meeting, January 11, 1982; cuid4394 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Board of Trustees -- Meeting, April 5, 1982; cuid4395 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Board of Trustees -- Meeting, November 4, 1982; cuid4396 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Board of Trustees -- Meeting, February 16, 1983; cuid4397 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Board of Trustees -- Meeting, May 16, 1983; cuid4398 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Board of Trustees -- Minutes, 1981-1983 (Box 81, Folder 2, Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Board of Trustees -- Piel, George, undated; cuid4399 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Board of Trustees -- Simmons, Richard D., undated; cuid4400 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Board of Trustees -- Stein, Elliot, undated; cuid4401 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Board of Trustees -- Straus, Roger, undated; cuid4402 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Brochures, 1979-1982 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Brochure, undated; cuid4403 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Budget, 1980-1983; cuid4404 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Budgets -- Proposed and Summaries, 1980-1994 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Budget Working Papers, 1980-1982 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Budget Working Papers, 1983-1984 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Budget Working Papers, 1985-1986 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Budget Working Papers, 1986-1989 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Budget Working Papers, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - By-Laws, 1978; cuid4405 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Committees -- General, 1979-2000 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Consortium -- Columbia University, 1980; cuid4406 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Consortium -- Graduate Center of the CUNY, 1980; cuid4407 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Consortium -- Hunter College, 1981; cuid4408 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Corporate Campaign, 1981-1983; cuid4409 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Culture in New York City Fellowship Program, 1979; cuid4410 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Director Search, 1978; cuid4411 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Dissolution Discussions, 1983-1996 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Doctoral Consortium in the Humanities and Social Thought Proposal, 1979; cuid4412 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Early Correspondence, 1977; cuid4413 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Event Schedules and Speaker Lists, September 2001 - December 2002; cuid4428 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Executive Committee, 1979-1980; cuid4414 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Executive Committee -- Meetings and Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Executive Committee -- Meetings and Correspondence, 1993-2001 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Executive Committee -- Correspondence and By-Laws Revisions, 2012-2013 (Box 92, Folder 1)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Materials in this folder are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Fellows - Correspondence and Rosters, 1980-1993 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Fellowship Committee, 1981-1995; cuid4415 (Box 3, Folder 2, Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Fellowship Applications, 1985-1986; cuid4416 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Fellowship Applications, undated; cuid4417 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Fifteen-Year Report, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 10, Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Five-Year Fellows Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Five-Year Report, 1982 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Friends' Campaign, 1983; cuid4418 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Fundraising Activities, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Fundraising Activities, 1981-1982 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Fundraising Activities, 1983-1985 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Fundraising Activities -- National Endowment for the Humanities, 1978-1982 (Box 82, Folder 4-5, Box 85, Folder 1-2)
    - General Correspondence and Press, 1976-1979 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence and Press, 1980-1984 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence and Press, 1985-1992 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence and Press, 1993 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence and Press, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence and Press, 1995-August 2004 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence, 2008-2012 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Grants -- General, 1983-2000 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Grants -- Open Society Institute, 2005 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Guidelines for the Institute, 1980-1981 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Guidelines for the Relationship between NYIH and NYU, 1981-1986 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Humanities Exchange Program, 1981-1984 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Invitations to Fellows, 1984-1985; cuid4419 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - List of Directors, 1976-2001 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Mailing List, 1988-1989; cuid4420 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - The New York Institute for Humanistic Studies Prospectus, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - New York University -- Central Administration, 1980-1983; cuid4421 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - New York University Contribution, 1979-1980; cuid4422 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - New York University -- NYIH Relationship, 1982; cuid4423 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Program Committee, 1979 and 1993-1999 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Relocation Planning, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Report to the Special Committee on the New York Institute for the Humanities, 1981; cuid4424 (Box 3, Folder 11, Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Search Committee, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Tax Exemption Statement for Challenge Grant, 1980; cuid4425 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Ten-Year Report, 1987; cuid4426 (Box 3, Folder 13, Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Thank-You Notes, 1993; cuid4427 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Subseries IB. Individuals, 1971-2012
    - Joann Akalaitis, undated; cuid4429 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Quentin Anderson, 1985-1988; cuid4430 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Lord Noel Annan, 1983; cuid4431 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Antonella Antonelli, 1985; cuid4432 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Charles Barber, 1984-1985; cuid4433 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Loren Baritz - Director, 1979; cuid4434 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Jennifer Bartlett, undated; cuid4435 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Francois Bedarida, 1979-1980; cuid4436 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Thomas Bender, 1976-1988; cuid4437 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Jessica Benjamin, 1978-1986; cuid4438 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Ivan Bennett, 1979-1981; cuid4439 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Isaiah Berlin, 1981; cuid4440 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Reinhard Bendix, 1977; cuid4441 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Leslie Berlowitz, 1994-1995 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Paul Berman, 1986; cuid4442 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Jeremy Bernstein, 1986; cuid4443 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Yvette Biro, 1985-1986; cuid4444 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Thomas Bishop, 1977-1988; cuid4445 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Jean Carey Bond, 1987-1988; cuid4446 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Thomas Bottomore, 1978; cuid4447 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Leon Botstein, 1977-1984; cuid4448 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Pierre Bourdieu, 1977-1980; cuid4449 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - John Brademas, 1982-1983; cuid4450 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Michael Brock, 1984; cuid4451 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Jerome Bruner, 1984-1989; cuid4452 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Jerome Bruner -- Correspondence, 1982-1985; cuid4453 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Jerome Bruner -- Resignation, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Peter Buckley, 1980-1986; cuid4454 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - McGeorge Bundy -- Appointment, 1979-1980; cuid4455 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Sarah Caldwell, 1983-1984; cuid4456 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Arnulf Conradi, 1984-1985; cuid4457 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Jill Sanchia Cowen, undated; cuid4458 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Vincent Crapanzano, 1986; cuid4459 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Xavier Rubert De Ventos, 1977; cuid4551 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Gabriel Dratwa, undated; cuid4460 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Norman Dorsen, 1985-1988; cuid4461 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Denis Donoghue, undated; cuid4462 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - E.L. Doctorow, 1985-1986; cuid4463 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Peggy C. Davis, 1985-1989; cuid4464 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Morris Dickstein, 1986; cuid4465 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Joseph D. Duffey, 1977; cuid4466 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Barbara Ehrenreich, 1979-1983; cuid4467 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Carol Feldman, 1985-1989; cuid4468 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Fellows, 1978-2012
      - Lists, Biographies, and Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - Lists, Biographies, and Correspondence, 1985-1990 (Box 86, Folder 2)
      - Scrapbook, 1986; cuid4757 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Lists, Biographies, and Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - Lists, Biographies, and Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - Biographies and Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - Lists, Biographies, and Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 86, Folder 6)
      - Lists, Biographies, and Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Lists, Biographies, and Correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - Lists and Photographs, 2005-2012 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - Photographs, undated (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Peter Fine, 1984; cuid4469 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Frances Fitzgerald, 1979-1983; cuid4470 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Lukas Foss, 1982; cuid4471 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Diane Foster, 1978; cuid4472 (Box 5, Folder 18)